<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Table schema: option to add a description to columns</title>
    <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/table-schema-option-to-add-a-description-to-columns/2589</link>
    <description>Hey,

Would be really helpful to have the ability to (manually) add a label and a description to each column each table schema, in order to give more details regarding the meaning of each column to team members who don&#39;t familiar with the DB structure.

In the system of the company I&#39;m working for, there&#39;re a lot of tables with a lot of misunderstood columns names (unless if you&#39;re someone from the developer team who query the DB a lot and got used to the names).

Anyway, it&#39;s becoming a problem with it comes to accessibility by other teams in the company who can&#39;t be sure what columns represents.

As a solution, I&#39;m currently giving them a dictionary stored in our internal knowledge base, by I thought about having this kind of docs inside Redash, as part of each table&#39;s schema.

What do you think? I&#39;m curious of other people here having this issue.</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:03:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Feature Requests</category>
    <atom:link href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/table-schema-option-to-add-a-description-to-columns/2589.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Table schema: option to add a description to columns</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[fish]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>I think it’s a great feature, I was looking for this feature, but couldn’t find it, I’m considering if I need to do custom development to support this feature.</p>
          <p><a href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/table-schema-option-to-add-a-description-to-columns/2589/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/table-schema-option-to-add-a-description-to-columns/2589/2</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 13:03:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">discuss.redash.io-post-2589-2</guid>
        <source url="https://discuss.redash.io/t/table-schema-option-to-add-a-description-to-columns/2589.rss">Table schema: option to add a description to columns</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Table schema: option to add a description to columns</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[nadavivry]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey,</p>
<p>Would be really helpful to have the ability to (manually) add a label and a description to each column each table schema, in order to give more details regarding the meaning of each column to team members who don’t familiar with the DB structure.</p>
<p>In the system of the company I’m working for, there’re a lot of tables with a lot of misunderstood columns names (unless if you’re someone from the developer team who query the DB a lot and got used to the names).</p>
<p>Anyway, it’s becoming a problem with it comes to accessibility by other teams in the company who can’t be sure what columns represents.</p>
<p>As a solution, I’m currently giving them a dictionary stored in our internal knowledge base, by I thought about having this kind of docs inside Redash, as part of each table’s schema.</p>
<p>What do you think? I’m curious of other people here having this issue.</p>
          <p><a href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/table-schema-option-to-add-a-description-to-columns/2589/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/table-schema-option-to-add-a-description-to-columns/2589/1</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 12:13:42 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">discuss.redash.io-post-2589-1</guid>
        <source url="https://discuss.redash.io/t/table-schema-option-to-add-a-description-to-columns/2589.rss">Table schema: option to add a description to columns</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
