<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Hosted Redash Replacement - Beekeeper Analytics</title>
    <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/hosted-redash-replacement-beekeeper-analytics/9008</link>
    <description>👋 Hey Redash community.

I&#39;m one of the maintainers of [Beekeeper Studio](https://beekeeperstudio.io), an open source SQL desktop app.

We love Redash and we&#39;re sad to see the hosted version shut down, so we&#39;re thinking of launching our own version of Hosted Redash and wanted to gauge interest.



If you are interested, please fill out the form [on the Beekeeper Analytics Website](https://dash.beekeeperstudio.io).

We&#39;re going to provide a **one-click migration** path and we&#39;re focusing on:

* **Full Compatibility** - All Redash features are replicated, nothing is missing.
* **Price Honoring** - Honoring the price you were paying for Hosted Redash.
* **Simple Migration** - A simple guided migration for all Redash data - queries, dashboards, users, and connections. Our migration will maintain query &amp; dashboard ownership and permissions.
* **Encryption** - All data will be encrypted at-rest and encrypted in transit with HTTPS. We will match or exceed existing Redash security practices.
* **Security** - We&#39;re committed to maintaining a secure environment by running regular external penetration tests.
* **Investment** - We have dedicated bandwidth to continue investment in Redash features, and the open source Redash community.

Hope to hear from some of you soon.

Matthew &amp; Gregory</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 21:24:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/hosted-redash-replacement-beekeeper-analytics/9008.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Hosted Redash Replacement - Beekeeper Analytics</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[rathboma]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/twitter/wave.png?v=10" title=":wave:" class="emoji" alt=":wave:"> Hey Redash community.</p>
<p>I’m one of the maintainers of <a href="https://beekeeperstudio.io" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">Beekeeper Studio</a>, an open source SQL desktop app.</p>
<p>We love Redash and we’re sad to see the hosted version shut down, so we’re thinking of launching our own version of Hosted Redash and wanted to gauge interest.</p>
<p>If you are interested, please fill out the form <a href="https://dash.beekeeperstudio.io" rel="noopener nofollow ugc">on the Beekeeper Analytics Website</a>.</p>
<p>We’re going to provide a <strong>one-click migration</strong> path and we’re focusing on:</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Full Compatibility</strong> - All Redash features are replicated, nothing is missing.</li>
<li>
<strong>Price Honoring</strong> - Honoring the price you were paying for Hosted Redash.</li>
<li>
<strong>Simple Migration</strong> - A simple guided migration for all Redash data - queries, dashboards, users, and connections. Our migration will maintain query &amp; dashboard ownership and permissions.</li>
<li>
<strong>Encryption</strong> - All data will be encrypted at-rest and encrypted in transit with HTTPS. We will match or exceed existing Redash security practices.</li>
<li>
<strong>Security</strong> - We’re committed to maintaining a secure environment by running regular external penetration tests.</li>
<li>
<strong>Investment</strong> - We have dedicated bandwidth to continue investment in Redash features, and the open source Redash community.</li>
</ul>
<p>Hope to hear from some of you soon.</p>
<p>Matthew &amp; Gregory</p>
          <p><a href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/hosted-redash-replacement-beekeeper-analytics/9008/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/hosted-redash-replacement-beekeeper-analytics/9008/1</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 21:24:57 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">discuss.redash.io-post-9008-1</guid>
        <source url="https://discuss.redash.io/t/hosted-redash-replacement-beekeeper-analytics/9008.rss">Hosted Redash Replacement - Beekeeper Analytics</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
