<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Can&#39;t migrate users</title>
    <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/cant-migrate-users/9302</link>
    <description>Hi there, 

I&#39;m having trouble migrating my users using `redash-migrate`. I had invited some users to the destination instance once I set it up and before the migration scripts were available.

I was able to properly migrate the data sources, but ran into some trouble when migrating users. I realized it was probably because of the users I had invited to the destination instance, so I manually added them to the `meta.json` only including their `id` and `email`. 

Once I did that, I was able to run `redash-migrate users`. The output showed:
```
CAUTION: user list is not in sync! Destination contains 57 users. Origin contains 343 users
```

All of the users that could not be migrated showed the same message:
```
Could not create user: probably this user already exists but is not present in meta.json
```

Something to note: I don&#39;t have Google Auth setup on the destination but it was enabled on the source instance – not sure if this could be an issue for those accounts.

Any idea on how I can rectify the remaining 286 accounts?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 01:30:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/cant-migrate-users/9302.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Can&#39;t migrate users</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jesse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p><img src="https://emoji.discourse-cdn.com/twitter/wave.png?v=10" title=":wave:" class="emoji" alt=":wave:"> thanks for your question. I haven’t seen this happen before but happy to help debug it and hopefully we can get a fix out soon.</p>
<p>The are three numbers that matter: how many users exist at</p>
<ol>
<li>the destination</li>
<li>the origin</li>
<li>meta.json</li>
</ol>
<p>The checker is telling you there are 57 at the destination and 343 at the origin. But how many appear in  your meta.json?</p>
<p>Ultimately we want all three numbers to be the same.</p>
<p>Also worth noting: the migration script assumes you are moving to a completely new instance. So this is a bit of an edge case. To narrow down the issue you could try spinning up a completely fresh instance and trying the migration. If even <em>that</em> fails then we can assume it’s an issue with google domains or etc.</p>
          <p><a href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/cant-migrate-users/9302/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/cant-migrate-users/9302/2</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 01:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">discuss.redash.io-post-9302-2</guid>
        <source url="https://discuss.redash.io/t/cant-migrate-users/9302.rss">Can&#39;t migrate users</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Can&#39;t migrate users</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[zackharley]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hi there,</p>
<p>I’m having trouble migrating my users using <code>redash-migrate</code>. I had invited some users to the destination instance once I set it up and before the migration scripts were available.</p>
<p>I was able to properly migrate the data sources, but ran into some trouble when migrating users. I realized it was probably because of the users I had invited to the destination instance, so I manually added them to the <code>meta.json</code> only including their <code>id</code> and <code>email</code>.</p>
<p>Once I did that, I was able to run <code>redash-migrate users</code>. The output showed:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">CAUTION: user list is not in sync! Destination contains 57 users. Origin contains 343 users
</code></pre>
<p>All of the users that could not be migrated showed the same message:</p>
<pre><code class="lang-auto">Could not create user: probably this user already exists but is not present in meta.json
</code></pre>
<p>Something to note: I don’t have Google Auth setup on the destination but it was enabled on the source instance – not sure if this could be an issue for those accounts.</p>
<p>Any idea on how I can rectify the remaining 286 accounts?</p>
          <p><a href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/cant-migrate-users/9302/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/cant-migrate-users/9302/1</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 15:44:14 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">discuss.redash.io-post-9302-1</guid>
        <source url="https://discuss.redash.io/t/cant-migrate-users/9302.rss">Can&#39;t migrate users</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
