<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel>
    <title>Date Range not getting updated on dashboard</title>
    <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/date-range-not-getting-updated-on-dashboard/10756</link>
    <description>Hey I have created the redash dashboard and have to change the date range to 4th July to 10th July. Everytime I update the dashboard using this date range and reopen it, the date range goes back to the previous week of 27th June to 3rd July, and then again I have to update the date range and refresh the dashboard. Is there a way to resolve this so that I don&#39;t have to do it each time I open the dashboard?</description>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 18:03:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <category>Usage Support</category>
    <atom:link href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/date-range-not-getting-updated-on-dashboard/10756.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <item>
        <title>Date Range not getting updated on dashboard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[jesse]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Welcome to the forum!</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Is there a way to resolve this so that I don’t have to do it each time I open the dashboard</p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>Short answer:</strong> yes but not easily.</p>
<p><strong>More complicated answer</strong>: the reason it reverts is that each parameter has a <em>default</em> value. It doesn’t remember the last value you used. It just uses the default. The default value of a parameter is the value that was used the last time you saved the <em>query</em>. To change the default value, you visit the query page, change the parameter value, and then save your changes.</p>
<p>In the case of <em>dashboards</em> this causes complexity because multiple queries can use the same parameter. So which query do you have to save to change the default on the dashboard? The answer is <em>the first query that was added to the dashboard</em>.</p>
<p>And unfortunately, there’s no way currently to tell which query was added to the dashboard first. So you have to use trial and error.</p>
<hr>
<p>The fix for this would be to store default parameter values <em>on the dashboard object</em>. This hasn’t been implemented. It will continue to be a pain point until we do.</p>
          <p><a href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/date-range-not-getting-updated-on-dashboard/10756/2">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/date-range-not-getting-updated-on-dashboard/10756/2</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 18:03:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">discuss.redash.io-post-10756-2</guid>
        <source url="https://discuss.redash.io/t/date-range-not-getting-updated-on-dashboard/10756.rss">Date Range not getting updated on dashboard</source>
      </item>
      <item>
        <title>Date Range not getting updated on dashboard</title>
        <dc:creator><![CDATA[Adarsh]]></dc:creator>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <p>Hey I have created the redash dashboard and have to change the date range to 4th July to 10th July. Everytime I update the dashboard using this date range and reopen it, the date range goes back to the previous week of 27th June to 3rd July, and then again I have to update the date range and refresh the dashboard. Is there a way to resolve this so that I don’t have to do it each time I open the dashboard?</p>
          <p><a href="https://discuss.redash.io/t/date-range-not-getting-updated-on-dashboard/10756/1">Read full topic</a></p>
        ]]></description>
        <link>https://discuss.redash.io/t/date-range-not-getting-updated-on-dashboard/10756/1</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 05:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
        <guid isPermaLink="false">discuss.redash.io-post-10756-1</guid>
        <source url="https://discuss.redash.io/t/date-range-not-getting-updated-on-dashboard/10756.rss">Date Range not getting updated on dashboard</source>
      </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
